Contact

winniexyan@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/winnieyanrn (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Patient Education

Patient Safety

Languages

Chinese (cantonese) (Native or Bilingual)

Chinese (mandarin) (Professional Working)

English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Adult-Gerontology Acute Care Nurse Practitioner (AGACNP-BC)

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS) certification

Basic Cardiac Life Support (BCLS) certification (CPR & AED)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS) certification

Critical Care Registered Nurse (Adult) (CCRN-A)

Honors-Awards

Valedictorian

McClure Scholarship

Cynthia Sculco Scholarship

Mckesson Foundation Scholarship

Arnold & Marie Schwartz Nursing Scholarship

Winnie Yan

Medical Intensive Care Unit Acute Care Nurse Practitioner Brooklyn, New York

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in post anesthesia recovery of multiple surgeries ranging from neurologic, thoracic, plastic, bariatric, to cardiac surgeries. ACLS and BCLS certified. ECMO, IABP, Impella, LVAD, and CRRT trained. Recently graduated from New York University's Acute Care Nurse Practitioner program.

Experience

NYU Langone Health

4 years 10 months

Acute Care Nurse Practitioner August 2019 - Present (10 months)

Medical Intensive Care Unit

CVSCU- Senior Staff Nurse

March 2016 - August 2019 (3 years 6 months)

Recovers patients directly after invasive open heart surgery (CABG, AVR, Septal Myectomy, and more). Special training received in ECMO, CRRT, IABP, Impella, and LVAD.

PACU- Staff Nurse

August 2015 - March 2016 (8 months)

Recovers both pediatric and adult patients undergoing neurologic, thoracic, gastrointestinal/genitourinary, bariatric, plastic, vascular, orthopedic, and general surgeries. Performs assessments on immediate post operative patients, manages post operative pain, anesthesia complications, and surgical sites. Initiates post-surgical treatment plans, communicates changes in patient status to the treatment team, advocates for patient safety, and educates patients and families on post-operative care.

NYU Hospital for Joint Diseases
Patient Care Technician

January 2015 - July 2015 (7 months)

Maintain comfort needs of patients and families. Assist with ambulation, transfer, and discharge of patients. Complete delegated responsibilities such as taking vital signs, obtaining blood glucose, performing electrocardiograms, and drawing blood.

NYU Hospital for Joint Diseases Student Nurse Extern June 2014 - August 2014 (3 months)

Worked under RN supervision to perform physical assessments, determine patient needs, implement care, provide patient education, and document patient responses. Expanded clinical skill set by performing EKGs, blood draws, catheterization, bladder scanning, suctioning and more in PACU, ICU, Medical- Surgical, and Neurological Rehabilitation settings. Actively participated in interdisciplinary team meetings.

MUJI U.S.A. Limited Sales Associate September 2011 - August 2013 (2 years)

Addressed customer needs and complaints. Presented product knowledge to ensure a pleasant shopping experience. Maintained store appearance with attention to detail by managing displays, replenishing floor stock, folding garments, and upholding the company's philosophy of simplicity and functionality. Experienced in performing transactions and returns.

Education

New York University

Master's degree, Adult-Gerontology Acute Care Nurse Practitioner

(AGACNP) · (2016 - 2019)

New York University
Bachelor of Science in Nursing (2011 - 2015)